iiab.com 2009-01-16

# Privacy

Geekdom Pty Limited (Geekdom) is committed to respecting the privacy of your personal information. This Website Privacy Notice explains our policy for dealing with personal information that we collect through our website, iiab.com ™.  

Throughout this policy, we refer to your 'personal information' which means information which identifies you as an individual or from which your identity can be reasonably ascertained. Your address is an example of personal information.  

We will post any changes to this Website Privacy Notice on iiab.com ™, so we encourage you to check this Website Privacy Notice from time to time.  

In addition to the provisions of this Website Privacy Notice, there may also be specific and additional privacy provisions that apply to certain sections of iiab.com ™. Because those specific and additional provisions also relate to your privacy protection, we recommend that you review them wherever they appear. In the event of any inconsistency between the provisions of this Website Privacy Notice and those other specific and additional provisions, the specific and additional provisions will prevail.

**1\. Information Collected**

The information about you which we may collect through iiab.com ™ includes:

  * information collected when you register or update an online profile, which may include personal information such as you and contact details 
  * the content of electronic forms you submit via iiab.com ™, requesting us to provide services or information 
  * any messages or comments you submit to us via iiab.com ™, eg through an email or 'Contact Us' form, and 
  * information collected when you participate in an online survey.

We may not be able to provide the full range of services through iiab.com ™ if we are not provided with the information outlined above.  

We automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, cookie information and the page you requested.  

**2\. Cookies**

We may set and access cookies on your computer. 'Cookies' are small identifiers sent from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, similar to a license plate, that help us to recognize you if you visit our website again. Also our website use cookies to track how you found our website. Cookies are not designed to be used to get data from your hard drive, your email or any other personal information about you. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet. You can reject cookies by changing your browser settings. Please note, however, that if you reject our cookies, it is possible that some web pages may not properly load, your access to certain information may be denied or you may have to enter information about you more than once. 

**3\. Use and disclosure of information**

We may share personal information with other service providers including organisations that assist us by providing archival, auditing, consulting, mailhouse, delivery, technology and security services.  
In addition to providing our services to you, we may use or disclose personal information that we collect about you: 

  * for the purposes for which it was collected 
  * where you have consented to the use or disclosure 
  * to maintain our relationship with you 
  * where a third party acquires or wishes to acquire, or makes inquiries in relation to acquiring, an interest in Geekdom; or 
  * to the extent that we are required or authorised by law to do so.

We may also use your personal information to keep you informed of our services, developments and other matters. If you do not wish to be contacted for those purposes, please let us know using the contact details set out below. We aim to provide you with information and invitations that we consider may be of interest or relevance to your business.  

**4\. Links**

iiab.com ™ may, from time to time, contain links to the websites of other organisations which may be of interest to you. Linked websites are responsible for their own privacy practices and you should check those websites for their respective privacy statements.

**5\. Security**

We use a number of mechanisms to protect the security and integrity of your personal information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the internet can be guaranteed as completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorised access, modification or disclosure.

iiab.com ™ protects your personal information by requiring you to use a password. For your own protection, we require you to keep this confidential and advise you to change your password regularly.  

For your safety and protection, your credit card information is not stored on our servers. Our payment gateway provider, PayFlow, keeps this information encrypted and secure on your behalf. 

**6\. Access to information**

If you wish to request access to any personal information which we hold about you as a result of our information collection practices outlined in this Website Privacy Notice, please contact us using the 'Contact details' set out below. Please provide as much detail as you can about the particular information you seek, in order to help us retrieve it. An access fee may be charged to cover our costs of providing the information to you.

**7\. Contact details**

If you have any questions or feedback about privacy, or wish to make a complaint about the way in which we have handled your personal information, you may contact us.

© Geekdom Pty Limited 2008. All rights reserved. Last updated: 5 December 2008
